{"pos": "verb", "term": "upswing", "correct_definition": "To swing upward.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.", "B: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.", "C: To swing upward.", "D: present participle and gerund of venture"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"upswing\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.\nB: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.\nC: To swing upward.\nD: present participle and gerund of venture\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "prebends", "correct_definition": "third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).", "B: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend", "D: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"prebends\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).\nB: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend\nD: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "polytechnic", "correct_definition": "that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: not rigid; flexible", "B: Able to be sustained.", "C: Not capitalized.", "D: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"polytechnic\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: not rigid; flexible\nB: Able to be sustained.\nC: Not capitalized.\nD: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "quadruplicate", "correct_definition": "To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.", "B: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback", "C: To draw along as a current does.", "D: present participle and gerund of chafe"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"quadruplicate\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\nB: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback\nC: To draw along as a current does.\nD: present participle and gerund of chafe\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "divorces", "correct_definition": "third-person singular simple present indicative of divorce", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: third-person singular simple present indicative of divorce", "B: present participle and gerund of potter", "C: To draw along as a current does.", "D: present participle and gerund of venture"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"divorces\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: third-person singular simple present indicative of divorce\nB: present participle and gerund of potter\nC: To draw along as a current does.\nD: present participle and gerund of venture\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "unlooked for", "correct_definition": "Not looked for, not searched for.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Not looked for, not searched for.", "B: Fitted with a cuff.", "C: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "D: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"unlooked for\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Not looked for, not searched for.\nB: Fitted with a cuff.\nC: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.\nD: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "odorized", "correct_definition": "Modified by addition of an odorant", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: Able to be sustained.", "B: Modified by addition of an odorant", "C: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "D: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"odorized\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Able to be sustained.\nB: Modified by addition of an odorant\nC: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nD: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "self report", "correct_definition": "Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.", "B: simple past and past participle of radium", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend", "D: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"self report\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.\nB: simple past and past participle of radium\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend\nD: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "conger", "correct_definition": "Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.", "B: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters", "C: Alternative form of gynesexual.", "D: A compline."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"conger\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.\nB: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters\nC: Alternative form of gynesexual.\nD: A compline.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "half-track", "correct_definition": "A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.", "B: A compline.", "C: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).", "D: The act of postulating or something postulated."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"half-track\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.\nB: A compline.\nC: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).\nD: The act of postulating or something postulated.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "chafing", "correct_definition": "present participle and gerund of chafe", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.", "B: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.", "C: present participle and gerund of chafe", "D: present participle and gerund of restaff"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"chafing\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.\nB: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\nC: present participle and gerund of chafe\nD: present participle and gerund of restaff\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "draw out", "correct_definition": "To physically extract, as blood from a vein.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: To physically extract, as blood from a vein.", "B: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback", "C: present participle and gerund of underwrap", "D: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"draw out\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To physically extract, as blood from a vein.\nB: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback\nC: present participle and gerund of underwrap\nD: Respond to something, such as a survey, with data about oneself.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "scutella", "correct_definition": "A scutellum.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: The act of postulating or something postulated.", "B: The pod of the snail clover.", "C: A scutellum.", "D: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"scutella\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: The act of postulating or something postulated.\nB: The pod of the snail clover.\nC: A scutellum.\nD: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "pettifog", "correct_definition": "To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: present participle and gerund of underwrap", "B: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).", "C: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.", "D: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"pettifog\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: present participle and gerund of underwrap\nB: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).\nC: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.\nD: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "red jade", "correct_definition": "A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.", "B: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.", "C: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "D: The act of supplementing"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"red jade\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.\nB: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.\nC: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\nD: The act of supplementing\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "Ommiad", "correct_definition": "Alternative form of Umayyad", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "B: Alternative form of Umayyad", "C: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.", "D: A compline."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"Ommiad\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\nB: Alternative form of Umayyad\nC: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.\nD: A compline.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "watercooler", "correct_definition": "Alternative spelling of water cooler", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "B: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "C: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.", "D: Alternative spelling of water cooler"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"watercooler\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\nB: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\nC: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.\nD: Alternative spelling of water cooler\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "cuffed", "correct_definition": "Fitted with a cuff.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: Alternative spelling of want-away", "B: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "C: Fitted with a cuff.", "D: Able to be sustained."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"cuffed\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Alternative spelling of want-away\nB: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nC: Fitted with a cuff.\nD: Able to be sustained.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "gynosexual", "correct_definition": "Alternative form of gynesexual.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).", "B: The act of postulating or something postulated.", "C: Alternative form of single-lens reflex", "D: Alternative form of gynesexual."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"gynosexual\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).\nB: The act of postulating or something postulated.\nC: Alternative form of single-lens reflex\nD: Alternative form of gynesexual.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "pottering", "correct_definition": "present participle and gerund of potter", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: To draw along as a current does.", "B: present participle and gerund of potter", "C: present participle and gerund of underwrap", "D: To take a shortcut over or through (a place)."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"pottering\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To draw along as a current does.\nB: present participle and gerund of potter\nC: present participle and gerund of underwrap\nD: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "restaffing", "correct_definition": "present participle and gerund of restaff", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: present participle and gerund of potter", "B: simple past and past participle of radium", "C: present participle and gerund of restaff", "D: present participle and gerund of venture"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"restaffing\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: present participle and gerund of potter\nB: simple past and past participle of radium\nC: present participle and gerund of restaff\nD: present participle and gerund of venture\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "profaner", "correct_definition": "One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.", "B: The act of supplementing", "C: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.", "D: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"profaner\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.\nB: The act of supplementing\nC: A red-coloured quartz mineral gemstone, red agate; it is not a normal jade mineral, being neither nephrite nor jadeite.\nD: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "sustainable", "correct_definition": "Able to be sustained.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "B: Fitted with a cuff.", "C: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects", "D: Able to be sustained."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"sustainable\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nB: Fitted with a cuff.\nC: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\nD: Able to be sustained.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "nonpermeable", "correct_definition": "Synonym of impermeable.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Fitted with a cuff.", "B: Not capitalized.", "C: Alternative spelling of want-away", "D: Synonym of impermeable."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"nonpermeable\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Fitted with a cuff.\nB: Not capitalized.\nC: Alternative spelling of want-away\nD: Synonym of impermeable.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "de minimis", "correct_definition": "Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: Not singing.", "B: Modified by addition of an odorant", "C: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "D: Fitted with a cuff."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"de minimis\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Not singing.\nB: Modified by addition of an odorant\nC: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nD: Fitted with a cuff.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "rite", "correct_definition": "A religious custom.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.", "B: A religious custom.", "C: Alternative form of gynesexual.", "D: confidence in one's own powers"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"rite\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: One who profanes; a person who desecrates or defiles.\nB: A religious custom.\nC: Alternative form of gynesexual.\nD: confidence in one's own powers\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "postulation", "correct_definition": "The act of postulating or something postulated.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A religious custom.", "B: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.", "C: Alternative form of Umayyad", "D: The act of postulating or something postulated."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"postulation\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A religious custom.\nB: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.\nC: Alternative form of Umayyad\nD: The act of postulating or something postulated.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "olive green", "correct_definition": "A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: Alternative form of Umayyad", "B: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "C: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "D: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"olive green\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Alternative form of Umayyad\nB: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\nC: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\nD: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "epipharyngeal", "correct_definition": "An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: A religious custom.", "B: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "C: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).", "D: Alternative form of Umayyad"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"epipharyngeal\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A religious custom.\nB: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\nC: A vehicle combining both wheels and treads (caterpillar tracks).\nD: Alternative form of Umayyad\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "overbank", "correct_definition": "To bank excessively", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: simple past and past participle of radium", "B: To draw along as a current does.", "C: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.", "D: To bank excessively"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"overbank\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: simple past and past participle of radium\nB: To draw along as a current does.\nC: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\nD: To bank excessively\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "nonrigid", "correct_definition": "not rigid; flexible", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "B: not rigid; flexible", "C: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "D: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"nonrigid\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nB: not rigid; flexible\nC: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.\nD: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "underwrapping", "correct_definition": "present participle and gerund of underwrap", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).", "B: simple past and past participle of radium", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend", "D: present participle and gerund of underwrap"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"underwrapping\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).\nB: simple past and past participle of radium\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend\nD: present participle and gerund of underwrap\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "Browning", "correct_definition": "A small, semi-automatic European handgun.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "B: A scutellum.", "C: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "D: A small, semi-automatic European handgun."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"Browning\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\nB: A scutellum.\nC: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\nD: A small, semi-automatic European handgun.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "phthiriasis", "correct_definition": "A pediculosis.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: A pediculosis.", "B: confidence in one's own powers", "C: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "D: A compline."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"phthiriasis\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A pediculosis.\nB: confidence in one's own powers\nC: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\nD: A compline.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "cut across", "correct_definition": "To take a shortcut over or through (a place).", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: To draw along as a current does.", "B: present participle and gerund of venture", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter", "D: To take a shortcut over or through (a place)."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"cut across\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To draw along as a current does.\nB: present participle and gerund of venture\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter\nD: To take a shortcut over or through (a place).\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "venturing", "correct_definition": "present participle and gerund of venture", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: present participle and gerund of venture", "B: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt", "C: To draw along as a current does.", "D: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"venturing\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: present participle and gerund of venture\nB: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt\nC: To draw along as a current does.\nD: To do a petty business as a lawyer, or carry out law business in a petty or tricky way.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "wayfaring", "correct_definition": "Travelling, especially on foot.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Travelling, especially on foot.", "B: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "C: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "D: Not looked for, not searched for."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"wayfaring\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Travelling, especially on foot.\nB: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nC: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nD: Not looked for, not searched for.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "supplementation", "correct_definition": "The act of supplementing", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.", "B: Alternative form of Umayyad", "C: Work done by digging with a spade.", "D: The act of supplementing"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"supplementation\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: An epipharyngeal bone or cartilage.\nB: Alternative form of Umayyad\nC: Work done by digging with a spade.\nD: The act of supplementing\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "entrain", "correct_definition": "To draw along as a current does.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: third-person singular simple present indicative of divorce", "B: To draw along as a current does.", "C: present participle and gerund of venture", "D: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"entrain\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: third-person singular simple present indicative of divorce\nB: To draw along as a current does.\nC: present participle and gerund of venture\nD: To replicate four times; to make fourfold; to quadruple.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "single lens reflex", "correct_definition": "Alternative form of single-lens reflex", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "B: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.", "C: confidence in one's own powers", "D: Alternative form of single-lens reflex"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"single lens reflex\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\nB: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.\nC: confidence in one's own powers\nD: Alternative form of single-lens reflex\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "radiumed", "correct_definition": "simple past and past participle of radium", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: present participle and gerund of venture", "B: present participle and gerund of restaff", "C: simple past and past participle of radium", "D: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"radiumed\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: present participle and gerund of venture\nB: present participle and gerund of restaff\nC: simple past and past participle of radium\nD: third-person singular simple present indicative of prebend\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "cauldron bottom", "correct_definition": "Used other than figuratively or idiomatically: see cauldron, bottom.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Alternative form of single-lens reflex", "B: Work done by digging with a spade.", "C: Alternative form of Umayyad", "D: Used other than figuratively or idiomatically: see cauldron, bottom."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"cauldron bottom\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Alternative form of single-lens reflex\nB: Work done by digging with a spade.\nC: Alternative form of Umayyad\nD: Used other than figuratively or idiomatically: see cauldron, bottom.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "Algherese", "correct_definition": "Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: Not singing.", "B: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "C: Able to be sustained.", "D: Not looked for, not searched for."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"Algherese\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Not singing.\nB: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.\nC: Able to be sustained.\nD: Not looked for, not searched for.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "panel", "correct_definition": "A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Work done by digging with a spade.", "B: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "C: Someone who leaves a country to settle in a new country.", "D: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"panel\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Work done by digging with a spade.\nB: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\nC: Someone who leaves a country to settle in a new country.\nD: A portion of text or other material within a book, newspaper, web page, etc. set apart from the main body or separated by a border.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "powters", "correct_definition": "third-person singular simple present indicative of powter", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: To bank excessively", "B: present participle and gerund of underwrap", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter", "D: present participle and gerund of restaff"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"powters\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: To bank excessively\nB: present participle and gerund of underwrap\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter\nD: present participle and gerund of restaff\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "uncapitalized", "correct_definition": "Not capitalized.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Not looked for, not searched for.", "B: Modified by addition of an odorant", "C: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "D: Not capitalized."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"uncapitalized\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Not looked for, not searched for.\nB: Modified by addition of an odorant\nC: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nD: Not capitalized.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "self-possession", "correct_definition": "confidence in one's own powers", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: confidence in one's own powers", "B: A pediculosis.", "C: The act of supplementing", "D: A small, semi-automatic European handgun."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"self-possession\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: confidence in one's own powers\nB: A pediculosis.\nC: The act of supplementing\nD: A small, semi-automatic European handgun.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "personal effects", "correct_definition": "Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: The pod of the snail clover.", "B: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.", "C: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)", "D: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"personal effects\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: The pod of the snail clover.\nB: A green-yellow hue that is brighter and greener than olive.\nC: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)\nD: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "completory", "correct_definition": "A compline.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.", "B: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)", "C: Alternative spelling of water cooler", "D: A compline."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"completory\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\nB: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)\nC: Alternative spelling of water cooler\nD: A compline.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "spadework", "correct_definition": "Work done by digging with a spade.", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Work done by digging with a spade.", "B: Alternative form of single-lens reflex", "C: A pediculosis.", "D: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"spadework\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Work done by digging with a spade.\nB: Alternative form of single-lens reflex\nC: A pediculosis.\nD: Items of personal property that one carries on one's person, including identification, jewelry, and clothing.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "emigrant", "correct_definition": "Someone who leaves a country to settle in a new country.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: Used other than figuratively or idiomatically: see cauldron, bottom.", "B: Someone who leaves a country to settle in a new country.", "C: Alternative form of gynesexual.", "D: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"emigrant\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Used other than figuratively or idiomatically: see cauldron, bottom.\nB: Someone who leaves a country to settle in a new country.\nC: Alternative form of gynesexual.\nD: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "quarterbacks", "correct_definition": "third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: simple past and past participle of radium", "B: present participle and gerund of restaff", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter", "D: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"quarterbacks\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: simple past and past participle of radium\nB: present participle and gerund of restaff\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter\nD: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "planimetric", "correct_definition": "relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "correct_answer": "C", "options": ["A: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "B: Extremely large-scale", "C: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "D: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"planimetric\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.\nB: Extremely large-scale\nC: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nD: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "snail", "correct_definition": "The pod of the snail clover.", "correct_answer": "D", "options": ["A: A religious custom.", "B: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)", "C: The act of postulating or something postulated.", "D: The pod of the snail clover."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"snail\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: A religious custom.\nB: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)\nC: The act of postulating or something postulated.\nD: The pod of the snail clover.\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "nonsinging", "correct_definition": "Not singing.", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter", "B: Not singing.", "C: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "D: Modified by addition of an odorant"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"nonsinging\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\nB: Not singing.\nC: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nD: Modified by addition of an odorant\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "verb", "term": "attempts", "correct_definition": "third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter", "B: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt", "C: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback", "D: present participle and gerund of underwrap"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"attempts\" mean in Indian English when used as a verb?\n\nA: third-person singular simple present indicative of powter\nB: third-person singular simple present indicative of attempt\nC: third-person singular simple present indicative of quarterback\nD: present participle and gerund of underwrap\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "noun", "term": "swipes", "correct_definition": "Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)", "B: A pediculosis.", "C: The act of supplementing", "D: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"swipes\" mean in Indian English when used as a noun?\n\nA: Synonym of swipe (\u201cpoor, weak beer or other alcoholic beverage\u201d)\nB: A pediculosis.\nC: The act of supplementing\nD: Any of several scaleless marine eels, of the genus Conger, found in coastal waters\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "megascale", "correct_definition": "Extremely large-scale", "correct_answer": "B", "options": ["A: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "B: Extremely large-scale", "C: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.", "D: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter"], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"megascale\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nB: Extremely large-scale\nC: Relating to Alghero, on the Italian island of Sardinia.\nD: relating to planimetry; made by means of a planimeter\n\nAnswer: "}
{"pos": "adjective", "term": "wantaway", "correct_definition": "Alternative spelling of want-away", "correct_answer": "A", "options": ["A: Alternative spelling of want-away", "B: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.", "C: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects", "D: Synonym of impermeable."], "prompt": "Which of the following could \"wantaway\" mean in Indian English when used as a adjective?\n\nA: Alternative spelling of want-away\nB: Concerning things that are so minor as to be negligible, trivial or trifling. Often used to describe exemptions in government rules and regulations.\nC: that teaches applied arts, sciences, technology, engineering and other academic subjects\nD: Synonym of impermeable.\n\nAnswer: "}
